National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
1972-2006, Undated
1981-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap298
27.55 cubic ft.
Since 1976 the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty has been working to educate the public about the failings and inconsistencies of capital punishment in the United States. Founded after the Gregg v. Georgia Supreme Court decision in 1976, the NCADP has emerged as one of the more influential national anti-death penalty organizations. The collection contains the group's internal case files, administrative material, publications, petitions, photographic materials, video tapes, and audio cassettes.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
The National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty transferred all items in this collection to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2007, 2018, 2022, and 2023.
Administrative History
The National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP) is the largest national organization exclusively devoted to abolishing the death penalty. The NCADP provides information, advocates for public policy, and mobilizes and supports individuals and institutions which reject the use of capital punishment. Through these methods the NCADP hopes to eliminate the death penalty in the United States and supports efforts to abolish the death penalty worldwide.
The NCADP was founded in 1976 following the Gregg v. Georgia Supreme Court decision, which reinstated the death penalty in the United States. Two American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) staff members, Deborah Leavy and Henry Schwarzchild, gathered a group of anti-capital punishment advocates one week after the Gregg decision. The organization that resulted brought together 26 affiliate organizations to coordinate their actions at the national level. The NCADP began its life housed within the ACLU offices in New York. Shortly after 1982 the group relocated to Philadelphia and, in 1987, moved to its current location in Washington D.C.
As a Washington based advocacy group, the NCADP lobbies against capital punishment through a variety of methods that include organizing protests and increasing public awareness. The NCADP uses a number of non-violent methods to draw attention to, and advance, their campaign at local, state and national levels.
Since its inception, the NCADP has been working to educate and inform the public about the failings and inconsistencies of the death penalty. The NCADP's campaign against capital punishment hinges on four core areas of advocacy: legislative, media, grassroots, and human rights. These efforts are accomplished through an annual conference, distribution of national publications such as LifeLines, the newsletter of the NCADP, and the National Execution Alert Network, a system which provides updates on pending executions. Founded in 1984, the Alert Network is a tracking and warning project keyed to executions – directing when and what actions should be taken in protest. Since 1981, the NCADP has hosted an annual conference which brings abolitionists from across the country together to analyze the past years successes and shortcomings and to strategize the goals and objectives for the coming year. Additionally, the NCADP compiles statistics and publishes findings on a variety of subjects concerning the death penalty including The Abolitionist Directory, a national listing of every organization and individual working against capital punishment and The Death Penalty Exchange, a handbook for organizers.
The NCADP has achieved recent victories in its struggle to end capital punishment. Through the efforts of its Stop Killing Kids Campaign, an initiative that sought to bring an end to the death penalty for offenders whose crimes were committed while they were under the age of 18, NCADP was successful in ending the death penalty as punishment for juveniles in several states. In 2006 NCADP successfully fought death penalty reinstatement efforts in Wisconsin, and the group has played a significant role in winning clemency for several death row inmates.
Scope and Contents
The National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records documents the administration, avocation, and lobbying activities of the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty from 1976 to 2001.
The largest portion of the collection contains the NCADP's internal case files. These are divided into Adult, Juvenile, and Innocence sub series comprised of folders which represent an individual capital case. Each file contains trial proceedings, news clippings, artwork, death warrants, and correspondence between the NCADP and death row inmates, government officials, and various affiliate organizations.
The NCADP Records also contain the group's publications, materials gathered from conferences, photographs, audio and video material, and signed petitions from the Stop Killing Kids campaign against the death penalty for juveniles.
The Subject Files series contains research material related to the various aspects of the death penalty but with a focus on education. Folders include material on death penalty law in the United States and abroad. Folders in this series contain articles, correspondence, news clippings, photographs, press releases, statements, and reports. Topics covered include advocacy, discrimination, families, juveniles, medical issues, and other aspects of death penalty law. This series also includes material from several affiliate organizations.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated
Subseries 1.1: Adults, 1988-2006, Undated
Subseries 1.2: Juveniles, 1994-2002, Undated
Subseries 1.3: Innocence, 1998-2000, Undated
Series 2 - Publications, 1982-2004, Undated
Series 3 - Subject Files, 1972-2005, Undated
Series 4 - Conferences, 1981-2005, Undated
Series 5 - Petitions, 1999
Series 6 - Photographs, 1976-2001, Undated
Series 7 - Audio, 1981-2005, Undated
Series 8 - Video, 1985-2005
This collection is grouped in to eight file series, the largest of which is the Case File which consists of the Adults, Juveniles, and Innocence subseries.
Death Penalty; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Capital punishment--Political aspects--United States; Capital punishment--Social aspects--United States; Capital punishment--United States; Capital punishment--United States--Cases; Political activists--20th century; Political activists--Legal status, laws, etc.; Political activists--United States; Case files; Correspondence; Criminal court records; Ephemera (general); Fliers (printed matter); Legal documents; Newspapers; Petitions; National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (U.S.)
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; 1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  Arrangement:
  Split into three subseries, Adults, Juveniles, and Innocence cases, and ordered alphabetically
  Contents:
  The NCADP collection is comprised mainly of case files. Files include newspaper clippings, publicity materials, and correspondence between the NCADP, inmates, lawyers, and family and friends. Some artwork, court transcripts, and death warrants are also present. Each folder represents a death penalty case that the organization was interested in or involved with.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; 1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    Alphabetical by last name
    Death row inmates over the age of 17
    - Abrecht, Alfred (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Adanandus, Dwight (TX), 1997 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Adcox, Keith (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Adkins, Ricky (AL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Ainsworth, Steven (CA), 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Akers, Thomas (VA), 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Alcala, Rodney (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Aldrich, Donald (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Aldridge, Rulford (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Alexander, Andre (CA), 1996 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Alexander, Caruthers (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Alfaro, Maria (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Allen, Gary (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Allen, Robert (DE), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Allen, Wanda (OK), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Allison, Watson (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Allridge, James (TX), 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Alston, Charlie (NC), 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Alvarez, Manuel Machado (CA), 1992 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Alvord, Gary E. (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Amaya-Ruiz, Jose (AZ), 2000; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Amos, Bernard (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Anderson, Michael (NE), 1995; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Anderson, Stephen (CA), 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Andrews, Jesse (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Apanovitch, Anthony (OH), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Apelt, Michael and Rudi (AZ), 1993; 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Appel, Martin (PA), 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Aranda, Arturo (TX), 1990; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Arias, Pedro (CA), 1996 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Armstrong, Lancelot (FL), 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Arnold, Jermarr (TX), 1991; 1994; 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Arnold, John D. (SC), 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Arther, Limmie (SC), 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Arther, Thomas (AL), 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Atkins, Daryl (VA), 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Atwood, Frank Jarvis (AZ), 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Atworth, Robert (TX), 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Avila, Johnny (CA), 1994 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Azania, Zulo A. (IN), 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Babbitt, Mannuel (CA), 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Bacigalupo, Miguel (CA), 1992; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Bacon, Robert (NC), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Baez, Orlando (PA), 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Bailey, Billy, (DE) Executed January 25, 1996, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Baird, Arthur (IN), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Baker, Wesley (MD), 2002; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Baldree, Ernest (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Baldwin, Brian (AL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Balfour, Susie (MS), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Banda, Esequel (TX), Executed December 11, 1995, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Banks Jr., Delma (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Bannister A.J (MO), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Barber, Danny (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Barbour, Christopher (AL), 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Barefield, John (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Barnabei, Derek (VA), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Barnes, Odell (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Barnes, Willis (TX), 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Basemore, William (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Bassette, Herbert (VA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Bates, Kayle B. (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Bates, Wayne (TN), 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Battle, Thomas (MO), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Baze, Ralph Jr. (KY), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Bean, Anthony (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Beardslee, Donald (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Beasley, Leslie (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Beathard, James (TX) [1 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Beathard, James (TX) [2 of 2], 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Beaty, Donald (AZ), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Beauer, Gregory (VA), 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Beauers, Thomas (VA), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Beets, Betty Lou (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Behringer, Earl "Duke" (TX) Executed June 11, 1997, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Bell, Larry (FL), 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Bell, Randy (AL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Bell, Steven (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Bell, Walter (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Bell, William H. (SC), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Belmontes, Fernando (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Bemore, Terry (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Beltron, Noe (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Belyeu, Clifton (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Benavides, Vincente (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Benefiel, Bill (IN), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Benn, Gary (WA), 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Bennett, Eric Wayne (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Bennett, Ronald (VA), 1996 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Berget, Roger (OK), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Berry, Earl W. (MS), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Berry, Wilford Lee (OH), 1997; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Berryman, Rodney (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Besaraba, Joseph (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Bey, Eric D. Clemmons (MO), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Bies, Michael (OH), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Bigby, James (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Billiot, James, (MS), 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Birdsong, Ralph "Hakim" (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Bittaker, Lawrence (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Bivins, Gernald (IN) [1 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Bivins, Gernald (IN) [2 of 2], 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Bjorklund, Roger (NE), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Black, Gary W. (MO), 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Blackmon, Ricky (TX), 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Blair, Michael (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Bland, Warren J. (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Blackenship, Roy (GA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Bloom, Robert (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Blystone, Scott (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Boggess, Clifford (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Bolden, Clifford (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Bolick, Jr., William (MO), 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Bolin, Oscar Ray (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Bolin, Paul (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Bond, Jesse (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Bonilla, Stephen (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Booker, Stephen (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Booth, John (MD), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Bottoson, Linroy (FL), 2002; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Bower, Lester (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Bowling, Thomas (KY), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Boyd, Arthur M. (NC), 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Boyd, Ronald (OK), 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Boyd, Russell Ernest (IN) and Gosch, Lesley (TX), 1993 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Boyd, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Boyle, Daniel L. (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Box, Christopher (CA), 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Bracy, Edward (PA), 1995; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Bracey, William (AZ), 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Bradford, Bill (CA), 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Bradford,Gayland (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Bradford, Mark (CA), 1990; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Bradley, Danny (AL), 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Branch, Erik S. (FL), 1994; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Breard, Angel Francisco (VA), 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Breedlove, McArthur (FL), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Brewer, John (AZ), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Brimage, Richard, Jr. (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Bronshtein, Antuan (PA), 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Brooks, Billy (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Broussard, Windell (TX), 2001 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Brown, Albert Greenwood, Jr. (CA), 1993 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Brown, Arthur Jr. (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Brown, Charles (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Brown, David (NC), 1998 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Brown, David J. (OK), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Brown, Deborah (IN), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Brown, Gary (AL), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Brown, James (GA), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Brown, John (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Brown, John (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Brown, Raymond E. (AL), 1991 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Brown, Vernon (MO), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Broxton, Eugene Alvin (TX), 1994 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Bruce, Kenneth (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Bryan, Anthony B. (FL), 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Bryan, Robert L. (OK), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Bryson, William (OK), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Buchanan, Doug (VA), 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Buenoano, Judi (FL), 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Buenrostro, Dora (CA), 1998 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Buhl, Kevin Lee (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Burdine, Calvin (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Burks, John (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Burns, William (TX), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Burris, Gary (IN), 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Burton, Andre (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Bush, John (FL), 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Bussell, Charles W. (KY), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Butler, Raymond (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Butler, Sabrina (MS), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Butler, Steven (TX), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Buttrum, Janice (GA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Byrd, John (OH), 1994; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Burdine, Calvin (TX), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Cade, Calvin (AL), 1993 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Cain, Burl (LA), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Cain, James (SC), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Calambro, Alvaro (NV), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Calderon, Arthur (CA), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Caldwell, Jeffrey (TX), 1991 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Callins, Bruce (TX), 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Camacho, Genaro R. (TX), 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Campbell, Charles (WA), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Campbell, James (FL), 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Campbell, Ken (TN), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Cannon, Joseph (TX), Executed April 22, 1998, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Cantu Jr., Domingo (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Cantu, Peter (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Cardona, Ana (FL), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Cargill, David L. (GA), 1998 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Caro, Fernando (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Carpenter, David (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Carpenter, David (FL), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Carpenter, James (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Carr, Darell Colenn (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Carriger, Paris (AZ), 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Carrington, Celeste (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Carroll, Robert (AL), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Carter, Dean (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Carter, Marcus (NC), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Carter, Robert (TX) [1 of 2], 1998; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Carter, Robert (TX) [2 of 2], Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Carter, Tracy (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Cartwright, Richard (TX), 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Caruthers, Alexander (TX), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Cash, Randall Scott (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Castro, Edward (FL), 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Castro, John (OK), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Cave, Alfonso (FL), 1993 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Cazaves, Jose Lupercio (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Ceja, Jose J. (AZ), 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Chaffee, Jonathan (SC), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Chambers, James W. (MO), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Chambers, Karl S. (PA), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Chambers, Tony (TX), 1994; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Chandler, Oba (FL), 1994 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Chandler, David R. (AL), 1994; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Chaney, Anthony Lee (AZ), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Chaney, Larry (FED), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Chappell, William Wesley (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Charping, James M. (SC), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Cheatham, Charles L. (OK), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Chester, Frank (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Chichester, Carl (VA), 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Christeson, Mark A. (MO), 2001 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)